<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> <rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://talksport.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"> <channel> <title>talkSPORT</title>
 <description>The world&#039;s biggest sports radio station</description>
 <link>http://talksport.com/</link>
 <atom:link rel="self" href="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans" />
 <language>en</language>
 <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:32:18 +0100</pubDate>
 <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:32:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
 <item> <title>CONFIRMED: Watford under investigation from EFL over allegations of ‘forged bank letter’</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/confirmed-watford-under-investigation-efl-over-allegations-forged-bank-letter-161025214732</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Watford are under investigation from the English Football League following allegations they supplied false financial documents during their 2014 takeover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Daily Telegraph’s report on Monday claimed the club forged a banking letter during Gino Pozzo&#039;s takeover of the Hornets, where he assumed complete control of the club from his father Giampaolo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The EFL have launched a full investigation, as the Hornets were a Championship club at the time, and they could hand down a hefty fine or even a points deduction should the allegations be found true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An EFL spokesman said: &quot;We can confirm, following receipt of information from the Daily Telegraph, that we immediately commenced a disciplinary investigation into serious allegations made against Watford Football Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;The club has been formally contacted by the EFL and is now required to provide a full and detailed response to the allegations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Once that response is received, it will be fully considered by the EFL and appropriate action will be taken under our rules and regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We will not be making any further comment until we are in receipt of the club&#039;s response.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hornets are currently ninth in the Premier League after taking 12 points from their opening nine games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The club released a statement to the Telegraph, saying: &quot;There are two ongoing investigations. It would be inappropriate to comment further until those investigations reach completion.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/confirmed-watford-under-investigation-efl-over-allegations-forged-bank-letter-161025214732</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:32:18 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/watford_0.jpg?itok=PUFJoBx5" fileSize="23509" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Watford could face a points deduction over the claims</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/watford_0.jpg?itok=JtoCi-5n" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Transfer rumours and paper review – Tuesday October 25: Rooney told he can leave Man United, Ozil and Sanchez set for new Arsenal deals and MORE</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/transfer-rumours-and-paper-review-tuesday-october-25-rooney-told-he-can-leave-man-united</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the top headlines and transfer-related stories in Tuesday&#039;s newspapers...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wayne Rooney could be set for the Manchester United exit door, amid claims that Jose Mourinho has told the club captain he will have to leave if he wants regular action.&lt;strong&gt; (The Sun)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the Red Devils players are reportedly surprised at Mourinho’s hands-off approach to training. &lt;strong&gt;(The Times)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arsenal chief Ivan Gazidis insists the club will begin to compete with their leading rivals over player wages, as they look to extend the contracts of Mesut Ozil, Alexis Sanchez and Hector Bellerin. &lt;strong&gt;(London Evening Standard)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manchester City are eyeing a £20million swoop for Bayern Munich&#039;s full-back Juan Bernat.&lt;strong&gt; (The Sun)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chelsea want to sign Antonio Rudiger from Roma for £35million, with Manchester United also reported to be interested. &lt;strong&gt;(Daily Mail)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Juventus are keen on signing Chelsea playmaker Oscar. The 25-year-old Brazilian is struggling to hold down a regular starting spot under Antonio Conte.&lt;strong&gt; (Calciomercato)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watford are ready to cash in on Nigerian striker Odion Ighalo, 27, amid interest from Napoli. &lt;strong&gt;(Watford Observer)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;West Ham are tracking Millwall defender Mahlon Rameo and are preparing a £1.5m bid for the 21-year-old. &lt;strong&gt;(Daily Mirror)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;West Brom are set to make a £4m move for Leeds left-back Charlie Taylor in January, after the 23-year-old rejected an extension to his contract at Elland Road that expires in the summer.&lt;strong&gt; (Daily Telegraph)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Latest talkSPORT.com headlines:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/listen-manchester-united-must-bring-back-sir-alex-ferguson-if-they-sack-jose-mourinho#Hyo7Jx2fuJ3laAdZ.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LISTEN: Manchester United MUST bring back Sir Alex Ferguson if they sack Jose Mourinho, former Premier League star tells talkSPORT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/manchester-city-fc-transfer-news-david-silva-could-be-next-star-ditched-ruthless-pep#376SxIj42oTtpdL1.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Manchester City FC transfer news: David Silva could be next star ditched by ruthless Pep Guardiola&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/everton-fc-transfer-news-manolo-gabbiadini-could-be-back-toffees-radar-napoli-consider-sale#DDiA5hi2WRW6ZWMu.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Everton FC transfer news: Manolo Gabbiadini could be back on Toffees&#039; radar as Napoli consider sale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/liverpool-transfer-report-napoli-attacker-lorenzo-insigne-keen-anfield-switch-161024214608#7SPoXAZVdcdRDCHL.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Liverpool transfer report: Napoli attacker Lorenzo Insigne keen on Anfield switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/liverpool-fc-transfer-news-athletic-bilbao-star-inaki-williams-dismisses-reports-he-could#AQKltgkZb35aD4X4.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Liverpool FC transfer news: Athletic Bilbao star Inaki Williams dismisses reports he could make £44.5m move to Anfield&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/transfer-news-bayern-munich-chief-rules-out-david-alaba-joining-pep-guardiola-manchester#FIlVoy6OSw7fJxTt.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Transfer news: Bayern Munich chief rules out David Alaba joining Pep Guardiola at Manchester City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/swansea-city-news-marseille-want-sign-bafetimbi-gomis-permanent-deal-161024214613#PCk3O0qfqsBDtQY4.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Swansea City news: Marseille want to sign Bafetimbi Gomis in permanent deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/thiago-silva-wants-extend-paris-saint-germain-stay-despite-interest-chelsea-manchester#rBfZ2PYA7cFw1FPx.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Thiago Silva wants to extend Paris Saint-Germain stay despite interest from Chelsea, Manchester United and Liverpool &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/tottenham-rival-napoli-race-sign-20-year-old-romanian-starlet-razvan-marin-161024214616#ZfSfyrXJzGbRwEEt.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tottenham to rival Napoli in race to sign 20-year-old Romanian starlet Razvan Marin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/chelsea-fc-transfer-news-ac-milan-defender-alessio-romagnoli-insists-he-has-no-interest#iB8tmcXEx0twarzF.99&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chelsea FC transfer news: AC Milan defender Alessio Romagnoli insists he has no interest in move&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/transfer-rumours-and-paper-review-tuesday-october-25-rooney-told-he-can-leave-man-united</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:05:57 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/transfer_rumours_-_june_2016_9.jpg?itok=0ByOBa8G" fileSize="196421" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Transfer Rumours and Paper Review</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/transfer_rumours_-_june_2016_9.jpg?itok=ZOdzrCTZ" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>West Ham United news: Hammers announce measures to prevent crowd trouble during EFL Cup clash v Chelsea</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/west-ham-united-news-hammers-announce-measures-prevent-crowd-trouble-during-efl-cup-clash-v</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Fans will face body searches at the turnstiles, alcohol restrictions, post-match segregation and a &quot;robust policing plan&quot; as part of measures aimed to minimise crowd trouble when West Ham host Chelsea in the EFL Cup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chelsea have been allocated just under 5,200 tickets for Wednesday night&#039;s fourth-round tie at London Stadium, which has been designated as a high-risk fixture given the history of animosity between the two sets of fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;West Ham moved from Upton Park into the converted Olympic Stadium for the start of the new season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been instances of disturbances in the stands during some Premier League fixtures, including against Watford and Middlesbrough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent matches have seen an increased line of segregation and also more stewards, as well as improved levels of training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In total, there have been nine arrests outside London Stadium, while 23 banning orders have been issued by West Ham, ranging from drinking in view of the pitch to breaking the line of segregation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Metropolitan Police Service says a &#039;&#039;tactical solution&#039;&#039; is now set for future games which would see officers deployed inside the ground if needed, despite the lack of a fully-operational Airwave radio system, which is used by the emergency services and now planned to be in place at London Stadium by February 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday evening, West Ham published on their website more information for supporters attending the cup tie and encouraged them to arrive early, with an &quot;enhanced body search policy&quot; to be implemented at the turnstile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ticket sales for home fans have been limited to supporters with a recorded purchase history at West Ham, while no alcohol will be sold pre-match from mobile bars outside the stadium. Those inside will be open as normal, albeit serving drinks in plastic cups, while there will be no post-match sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Met Police will also &quot;continue to provide an appropriate and visible presence&quot; outside the game, with supporters able to mix freely before the match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, however, segregation will be in place outside the away turnstile along with a cordon as Chelsea fans are directed via the south steps towards Pudding Mill Lane Docklands Light Railway Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All supporters will be informed of any changes to these plans on the night via the stadium public address system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the article, West Ham highlighted &quot;the overwhelming majority of supporters attending matches at London Stadium so far this season have behaved impeccably during their visits&quot;, but also restated the club&#039;s &#039;zero tolerance policy&#039; which will see any Irons&#039; fans &quot;found to be acting inappropriately... identified and dealt with accordingly&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson for London Stadium partners West Ham, E20 Stadium LLP and London Stadium 185 said there was confidence the new measures implemented since the start of the season have proven successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;The depth of the line of segregation between home and visiting fans at London Stadium was made significantly wider after the game against Watford with additional stewards deployed in that area. This new line of segregation was implemented at the Accrington Stanley (EFL Cup) game,&quot; the spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We have had no issues with the new segregation and we have had positive feedback from supporters in that area and consider this early issue to now be resolved.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spokesperson added: &quot;The Metropolitan Police Service have been working closely and effectively with all London Stadium stakeholders ahead of the Chelsea game, and there is a robust policing plan in place to deal with crime and disorder and support all the stakeholders in making this a safe event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;The match against Chelsea will have significant resources deployed to prevent any breach of peace or unsocial behaviour, and help ensure a safe and family friendly environment for all London Stadium visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;All stadium partners are committed to a zero tolerance policy to anti-social behaviour, inside and outside the London Stadium and will not hesitate to take action.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/west-ham-united-news-hammers-announce-measures-prevent-crowd-trouble-during-efl-cup-clash-v</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 22:38:03 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617254636.jpg?itok=Kv1ntEet" fileSize="163349" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">West Ham have laid out measures to prevent crowd trouble against Chelsea</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617254636.jpg?itok=-9ymUabc" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Manchester United FC news: Jose Mourinho urges Red Devils stars to prove they are &#039;men&#039; in EFL Cup clash v Manchester City</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/manchester-united-fc-news-jose-mourinho-urges-red-devils-stars-prove-they-are-men-efl-cup</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Manchester United manager Jose Mourinho has warned his players there is &quot;no way to hide&quot; and challenged them to show they are &quot;men&quot; by recovering from the 4-0 humiliation at Chelsea by beating Manchester City in the EFL Cup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday saw a six-match unbeaten run in all competitions come to a comprehensive end as Mourinho and many of the United coaching staff endured a nightmare afternoon at their old stomping ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pedro&#039;s goal after 30 seconds threw the visitors off kilter at Stamford Bridge, with Gary Cahill, Eden Hazard and N&#039;Golo Kante all scoring as the Blues went on to handed out a chastening defeat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wednesday will be the second time City boss Pep Guardiola and Mourinho have faced one another since taking up residency in Manchester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A swashbuckling display - despite a nervy debut for Claudio Bravo - saw City run out 2-1 victors at Old Trafford when the sides met in the Premier League last month, with the upcoming EFL Cup fourth-round encounter at the same venue offering both the chance to get things back on track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mourinho expects a reaction from his players, who are now five points behind of the top four in seventh place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I would prefer to play (next) in the Premier League. It&#039;s a bad feeling in the Premier League. With the combination of results the gap to the top is six points,&quot; Mourinho said in an interview with MUTV after the Chelsea match and looking ahead to the cup tie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We have had a very difficult period of matches. We lost points this week and, even in the match when we played phenomenal against Stoke, we lost points then. Now we need to win matches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I am not saying they are easy ones, but we have Burnley, we have Swansea, West Ham, Sunderland, Middlesbrough - matches that we need to win and the top four, the top five, they have to play between themselves like we did this week against Chelsea and Liverpool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;They are going to lose points too, so we are in the run, but there is no way to hide because I think our faces speak by themselves.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mourinho added: &quot;We are really, really sad, but again this is not for kids, this is for men and...we have to be men and work for the next one.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Former Chelsea midfielder Juan Mata, who was introduced at half-time against his old club, says the scoreline &quot;hurts&quot;, but knows United can ill-afford to wallow in self-pity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We must carry on. Luckily, in three days we have a very important fixture, and as from now we must focus on this new opportunity to get better,&quot; Mata wrote on his blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It sounds like a cliche but it&#039;s true: when we win and everybody praises you it&#039;s easy to be united and celebrate together, but it is now, after such a defeat, when we must remain mentally strong and keep going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Together we win and together we lose.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/manchester-united-fc-news-jose-mourinho-urges-red-devils-stars-prove-they-are-men-efl-cup</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 22:25:37 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617452538_0.jpg?itok=2D02-dD_" fileSize="43350" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Jose Mourinho has challenged his players to improve from their disastrous showing at Chelsea</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617452538_0.jpg?itok=uO4vbuhL" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>CONFIRMED: Anthony Joshua will NOT fight Wladimir Klitschko as former heavyweight champion suffers injury</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/boxing/confirmed-anthony-joshua-will-not-fight-wladimir-klitschko-former-heavyweight-champion</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Anthony Joshua&#039;s proposed world heavyweight title fight with Wladimir Klitschko on December 10 will not go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Promoter Eddie Hearn announced on Monday evening that, with the Ukrainian suffering from a &quot;minor injury&quot; and no decision over whether the WBA title would be on the line, the fight could not happen on the date suggested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearn told Sky Sports: &quot;We&#039;ve been in deep negotiations for a few weeks now waiting on the decision from the WBA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I was made aware that Wladimir picked up a minor injury late last week but regardless of that, with just over six weeks to go until December 10, it&#039;s unrealistic to put together a fight of this magnitude and give it the full build-up it deserves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;There will be an official announcement on Joshua v Klitschko coming very soon, but for now we are seeking a new foe for December 10 and building a huge card for Manchester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearn said just over a week ago that &quot;terms are virtually there&quot; for a fight between Joshua and Klitschko, only for the wait for WBA sanctioning to delay the deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Klitschko lost the WBA belt to Tyson Fury last November, along with the IBF title. The latter sanctioning body insisted on a rematch, leading Fury to vacate that belt which was won by Joshua against Charles Martin in April. He then defended it against Dominic Breazeale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fury then relinquished his remaining WBA, WBO and IBO titles earlier this month and stepped away from the sport to battle mental health issues. He also admitted regularly using cocaine and was stripped of his licence by the British Boxing Board of Control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Klitschko appeared unwilling to fight Joshua without the WBA belt being on the line and is reportedly set to fight Australia&#039;s&lt;br /&gt;
Lucas Browne for that title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joshua&#039;s opponent on December 10 could now be IBF mandatory challenger Joseph Parker, Bulgaria&#039;s Kubrat Pulev or fellow British Olympian David Price. Parker has indicated he is more likely to fight Andy Ruiz Jr for the WBO title in his native New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/boxing/confirmed-anthony-joshua-will-not-fight-wladimir-klitschko-former-heavyweight-champion</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 20:58:35 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/pjimage_1_7.jpg?itok=elB0f_Jw" fileSize="86952" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Anthony Joshua will not fight Wladimir Klitschko in December</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/pjimage_1_7.jpg?itok=X0cGqQ0a" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>&#039;This week just gets better being a Chelsea fan&#039; - Blues supporters react as Kurt Zouma returns to action</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/week-just-gets-better-being-chelsea-fan-blues-supporters-react-kurt-zouma-returns-action</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Chelsea fans were delighted on Sunday following the stunning win over Manchester United, and things got even better for the Blues on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kurt Zouma returned to action for their development side, playing the first half against Derby County.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was the French defender&#039;s first action since February, when he picked up an ACL injury in a match against Manchester United.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regarded by many as the finest defender in the current Chelsea squad, fans want to see him back in action as soon as possible, and his return to match action was warmly greeted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He may have endured a tough time against the Rams, conceding a penalty from which they scored the opening goal, but fans could show nothing but delight at the news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check out some of the best reactions to Zouma&#039;s return below...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;iframe allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; height=&quot;750&quot; src=&quot;//storify.com/talksport/this-week-just-gets-better-being-a-cfc-fan/embed?border=false&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/week-just-gets-better-being-chelsea-fan-blues-supporters-react-kurt-zouma-returns-action</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 20:38:54 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/zouma.jpg?itok=AzeOqj-j" fileSize="21867" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Kurt Zouma is back in action for Chelsea</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/zouma.jpg?itok=djZI3D3V" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Tottenham Hotspur FC team news: Mauricio Pochettino confirms Michel Vorm will replace Hugo Lloris for EFL Cup clash v Liverpool</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/tottenham-hotspur-fc-team-news-mauricio-pochettino-confirms-michel-vorm-will-replace-hugo</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Mauricio Pochettino has confirmed Hugo Lloris will sit out of Tottenham’s EFL Cup clash against Liverpool on Tuesday, with Michel Vorm set to replace the French keeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vorm has made four appearances so far this season, starting the first three games of the Premier League season when Lloris was out of action through injury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also played in Spurs’ previous EFL Cup fixture - a 5-0 win over Gillingham - and Pochettino has lined up Vorm for another start against the Reds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He impressed in his showings in the early weeks of the season, and the Argentine manager insisted he deserves to play  - especially as Lloris is not a ‘machine# who can play every match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It&#039;s true that tomorrow we&#039;ll play Michel Vorm,&quot; said Pochettino.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Hugo is not a machine, he&#039;s one of the best but he&#039;s not a machine. Tomorrow is a very good opportunity for Michel, he deserves to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Players like Lloris, they are not machines. And it is very tough to go from international matches, to the Premier League, to the Champions League and back to the Premier League, without any breaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;So we will rotate and we will rotate in the next few games too, because it&#039;s important that the whole squad feel they are important, have the chance to play and show their quality.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/tottenham-hotspur-fc-team-news-mauricio-pochettino-confirms-michel-vorm-will-replace-hugo</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:24:58 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/michel_vorm.jpg?itok=XopVVKdK" fileSize="22218" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Michel Vorm has made four appearances this season</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/michel_vorm.jpg?itok=VcivgNG7" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Leicester star Jamie Vardy only Englishman nominated for 2016 Ballon d&#039;Or - full shortlist revealed</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/leicester-star-jamie-vardy-only-englishman-nominated-2016-ballon-dor-full-shortlist</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Jamie Vardy has been nominated for the Ballon d&#039;Or award alongside the likes of Cristiano Ronaldo, Lionel Messi and Gareth Bale after helping Leicester win the Premier League title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 29-year-old striker, who scored 24 goals in a historic season for the Foxes, was named on a 30-man list of nominees for the prestigious award, which is currently held by Barcelona star Messi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;France Football, the sole organisers of the prize given to the best footballer in the world following a split from FIFA, revealed Vardy was in contention in a tweet published on Monday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sheffield-born player is the only Englishman nominated, while Real Madrid&#039;s Bale represents Wales after his heroics at Euro 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vardy is not the only Leicester player whose achievements have been recognised, however. Algerian winger Riyad Mahrez - the PFA Players&#039; Player of the Year - is on the shortlist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manchester City and city rivals United will hope Sergio Aguero, Kevin De Bruyne, Zlatan Ibrahimovic and Paul Pogba threaten the top three when journalists begin the next round of voting, while West Ham&#039;s free-kick specialist Dimitri Payet and Tottenham goalkeeper Hugo Lloris are also contenders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regular victors Messi and Ronaldo - the latter having endured a lean year by his usual prolific standards - will face stiff competition from the likes of Luis Suarez, Neymar and Robert Lewandowski.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakthrough stars Paulo Dybala, Antoine Griezmann and Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang will provide further cause for concern to the world game&#039;s established top order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the surprise omissions from the list are Manchester United keeper David De Gea, Arsenal playmaker Mesut Ozil and Juventus centre-back Leonardo Bonucci.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ballon d&#039;Or 2016 shortlist in full:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sergio Aguero (Manchester City)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang (Borussia Dortmund)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gareth Bale (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gianluigi Buffon (Juventus)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cristiano Ronaldo (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin De Bruyne (Manchester City)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paulo Dybala (Juventus)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diego Godin (Atletico Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antoine Griezmann (Atletico Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gonzalo Higuain (Juventus)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zlatan Ibrahimovic (Manchester United)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andres Iniesta (Barcelona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Koke (Atletico Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toni Kroos (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Lewandowski (Bayern Munich)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas Muller (Bayern Munich)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luka Modric (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Riyad Mahrez (Leicester)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lionel Messi (Barcelona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo Lloris (Tottenham)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dimitri Payet (West Ham)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul Pogba (Manchester United)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manuel Neuer (Bayern Munich)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pepe (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neymar (Barcelona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rui Patricio (Sporting Lisbon)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sergio Ramos (Real Madrid)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luis Suarez (Barcelona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jamie Vardy (Leicester)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arturo Vidal (Bayern Munich)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/leicester-star-jamie-vardy-only-englishman-nominated-2016-ballon-dor-full-shortlist</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:11:08 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/pjimage_22.jpg?itok=zVxqZbkv" fileSize="100848" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Jamie Vardy, Paul Pogba and Dimitri Payet and three of eight Premier League players on the Ballon d&#039;Or shortlist</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/pjimage_22.jpg?itok=sbZJg-FT" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>‘We accept the charge’ - Mauricio Pochettino reveals Tottenham will NOT contest Moussa Sissoko violent conduct charge</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/we-accept-charge-mauricio-pochettino-reveals-tottenham-will-not-contest-moussa-sissoko</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Tottenham have no plans to contest the Football Association’s violent conduct charge against Moussa Sissoko, with manager Mauricio Pochettino expecting the French midfield to receive a three-match ban.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sissoko &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://talksport.com/football/tottenham-midfielder-moussa-sissoko-charged-violent-conduct-elbow-bournemouths-harry-arter&quot;&gt;has been charged by the FA for his off-the-ball elbow of Bournemouth&#039;s Harry Arter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; that was missed by officials in Saturday&#039;s goalless Premier League draw at the Vitality Stadium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The £30million summer signing from Newcastle should now be banned for Tuesday&#039;s EFL Cup tie at Liverpool and Premier League matches against Leicester and bitter rivals Arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spurs have until 18:00BST on Tuesday to respond to the charge, but Pochettino revealed the club will not contest the potential suspension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We accept that,” the Argentine said. “We have reviewed the video. We accept the charge and now we move forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;After the game it was difficult when I was asked about the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It was true that it was difficult for me to appreciate the situation of what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;But when I saw it on TV I need to say there was no intention but the elbow was in the face of Arter, that&#039;s clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We accept the charge, and now we need to move forward, and expect a three-match ban.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sissoko&#039;s anticipated three-match absence comes at a hectic time for the Lilywhites, with the north London side playing Liverpool, Leicester, Leverkusen and Arsenal in a run of four challenging games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pochettino has admitted losing Sissoko is a worry, as he wanted all of his squad available for the impending matches, but the manager insisted the Frenchman had no need to apologise for his actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asked if Sissoko&#039;s impending ban is a blow, Pochettino added: &quot;That is true, because we are in a period that we need all the squad, all the players fit to compete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;We have a big four games, Liverpool, Leicester, Leverkusen and Arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It&#039;s true that it&#039;s difficult now, because he&#039;s a player that was in our plans to play tomorrow, and now we need to change a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I believe in him, that it wasn&#039;t intentional, but the action happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;It wasn&#039;t his intention for that to happen. Sometimes that happens during matches.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/we-accept-charge-mauricio-pochettino-reveals-tottenham-will-not-contest-moussa-sissoko</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 17:02:58 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-613810288.jpg?itok=mZU_PcyJ" fileSize="65072" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Moussa Sissoko is facing a three-match ban for his off-the-ball elbow of Bournemouth&#039;s Harry Arter</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-613810288.jpg?itok=4fPTO3ry" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Fastest footballers so far in the 2016/17 Premier League season – top 10 revealed</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/fastest-footballers-so-far-201617-premier-league-season-top-10-revealed-161024214697</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Speed is vital in the modern game, but who are the fastest footballers in the Premier League?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Opta stats, the 10 players revealed above are the speediest in the top flight, at least as it stands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the slideshow above to see which players feature and let us know what you think of the list by leaving a comment below.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/fastest-footballers-so-far-201617-premier-league-season-top-10-revealed-161024214697</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:58:41 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:group> <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/10bellerin.jpg?itok=Z0eD2UnK" fileSize="32864" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/8walcott.jpg?itok=g34O6xto" fileSize="12401" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/8yoshida.jpg?itok=CEW7SCvt" fileSize="28631" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/7zaha.jpg?itok=zqkgBp6_" fileSize="46919" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/6bailly.jpg?itok=b_gZ_fEN" fileSize="25519" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/5gray.jpg?itok=fL3DEZyP" fileSize="50483" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/4vardy.jpg?itok=G8pf-sps" fileSize="34779" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/3walker.jpg?itok=fHrK2d-r" fileSize="38323" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/2lyndengooch.jpg?itok=AJhFzNIz" fileSize="46108" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/1shanelong.jpg?itok=BDU2mhwE" fileSize="44968" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420" />
</media:group>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/10bellerin.jpg?itok=SO7O5EhO" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/8walcott.jpg?itok=CKnThM3M" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/8yoshida.jpg?itok=SmpND1_2" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/7zaha.jpg?itok=BKj9cvVy" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/6bailly.jpg?itok=C9GGf7vl" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/5gray.jpg?itok=p1WNBIWj" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/4vardy.jpg?itok=cLtQ8kDG" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/3walker.jpg?itok=WGBN8hBI" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/2lyndengooch.jpg?itok=C-68BAnC" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/1shanelong.jpg?itok=LzB5Eupf" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>&#039;We have a number one and that&#039;s Loris Karius&#039; - Jurgen Klopp says Simon Mignolet is now Liverpool&#039;s back-up goalkeeper</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/we-have-number-one-and-thats-loris-karius-jurgen-klopp-says-simon-mignolet-now-liverpools</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Simon Mignolet will return for Liverpool in the EFL Cup - but manager Jurgen Klopp has made it clear the Belgian goalkeeper is now second choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mignolet has had three inconsistent seasons at Anfield and lost his place to new signing Loris Karius for the Reds&#039; defeat of Derby in the third round of the competition last month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time Klopp said he had no definite number one but, with Karius having now played five games in succession, his thoughts have changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mignolet, however, remains a key figure in the squad and Klopp is keen to have him involved as Tottenham visit Anfield in the fourth round on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Klopp said: &quot;If nothing happens in training then he will play, 100 per cent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;But in this moment we have a number one and that&#039;s Loris Karius. That&#039;s the situation and what the goalkeepers know. I cannot leave them in doubt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;There was a short period with the two or three games we (initially) gave Loris to see a little bit more of him, but after the last international break I spoke to both of them and we made this decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Of course, he (Mignolet) was not happy about this but nobody can see this in training. He is still working hard, improving, (doing) all that he has to do. He is a very serious person and a good professional.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liverpool have lost just once in 11 games in all competitions this season and Saturday&#039;s victory over West Brom has left them joint top of the Premier League with Manchester City and Arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That has fuelled further talk of a title challenge but Klopp is not interested in outside opinions at this stage of the season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;I don&#039;t care,&quot; the German said. &quot;It&#039;s normal in football that when you are in a good position people starting talking a little bit more positive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;But I don&#039;t recognise too much what everybody is saying about us. Of course I recognise the mood around LFC and it&#039;s good, but we&#039;re still in October. There&#039;s a long way to go so there is nothing to say about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Nothing we have done up until now has been close to 100 per cent. We have to improve a lot of things.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liverpool were beaten in the final of the League Cup last season, losing on penalties to Manchester City. Klopp wants to go one better this time but insists putting right February&#039;s Wembley loss is not the prime motivation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He said: &quot;It&#039;s a negative sign if we lose a final we say we want to win it next year. It&#039;s a very big cup tournament. That is the reason we want to go to the final and win.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Klopp said at the weekend he would welcome the prospect of Steven Gerrard returning to Anfield in some capacity following hints by the former Reds captain he could soon leave the LA Galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But asked if there had been any further developments, Klopp said at a press conference: &quot;There is nothing else to say about it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/we-have-number-one-and-thats-loris-karius-jurgen-klopp-says-simon-mignolet-now-liverpools</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:42:58 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/simonm.jpg?itok=1s67B1gF" fileSize="37463" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Simon Mignolet</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/simonm.jpg?itok=gO6qX8s6" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Huge England BLOW as Saracens confirm Maro Itoje will miss entire autumn international campaign</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/rugby-union/huge-england-blow-saracens-confirm-maro-itoje-will-miss-entire-autumn-international</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;European player of the year Maro Itoje will miss England&#039;s autumn Tests after fracturing his right hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itoje&#039;s club Saracens confirmed the injury, which happened during Saturday&#039;s European Champions Cup victory over the Scarlets at Allianz Park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saracens say that second-row forward Itoje requires surgery and will be sidelined for six weeks. It will rule him out of England&#039;s games against South Africa, Fiji, Argentina and Australia, and is a huge blow for club and country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the latest in a number of major injury setbacks for England head coach Eddie Jones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jones has already lost the likes of Itoje&#039;s Saracens and England second-row partner George Kruis for the autumn, in addition to players like James Haskell, Anthony Watson and Jack Clifford.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a statement released by Saracens, the club&#039;s rugby director Mark McCall said: &quot;For any team to lose a player of the ability of Maro is a blow, and he will be missed through the autumn for both Saracens and England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;What&#039;s now important for Maro is his recovery, and we look forward to his return later this season.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jones is due to announce his squad for the autumn games on Wednesday, and England will go into those Tests on the back of a nine-match winning run since he took charge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itoje, 21, was replaced in the 46th minute of Saracens&#039; 44-26 victory over the Scarlets after his arm was trapped awkwardly while making a tackle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And of all the injury blows Jones has faced, Itoje&#039;s loss is arguably the most significant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has made rapid strides to world-class status in a remarkably short space of time, starring for England and Saracens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itoje helped England to Six Nations title and Grand Slam glory last season, then started all three games when Jones&#039; team claimed a 3-0 Test series whitewash against Australia Down Under.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And he was a hugely-influential figure during Saracens&#039; march to winning the European Champions Cup and retaining the Aviva Premiership title last term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Itoje and Kruis sidelined, it looks as if Jones will now turn to seasoned campaigners Joe Launchbury and Courtney Lawes for the Springboks clash on November 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itoje had also been talked about as an openside flanker option for Jones, with Haskell and other candidates like Leicester&#039;s Mike Williams and Wasps&#039; Sam Jones all injured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the Australian will now have to look elsewhere as he faces a serious test of his resources.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/rugby-union/huge-england-blow-saracens-confirm-maro-itoje-will-miss-entire-autumn-international</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:26:10 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/itoje.jpg?itok=XnAXDg0v" fileSize="39077" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Maro Itoje in action for Saracens</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/itoje.jpg?itok=0lqNSKLG" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Burnley fan celebrates Premier League win over Everton... by taking a horse to the pub! (video)</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/burnley-fan-celebrates-premier-league-win-over-everton-taking-horse-pub-video-161024214674</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Burnley recorded just their third Premier League win of the season on Saturday, beating Everton thanks to Scott Arfield&#039;s last-gasp winner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a momentous occasion for the Clarets, and one which led to a rather random celebration from a fan of Sean Dyche&#039;s team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As many football fans do, this fan decided to celebrate the win with a trip to the pub - but he did not show up alone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, he decided to take a HORSE with him to his local, riding it in to great fanfare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check it out below...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;media_embed&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-video&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot; height=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot; xml:lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;Burnley fan casually shows up down his local on a horse yesterday after beating Everton 2-1. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/UTC?src=hash&quot;&gt;#UTC&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/uBi1hu34Qq&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/uBi1hu34Qq&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Away Days Videos (@AwayDaysVideos) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AwayDaysVideos/status/790130061278052352&quot;&gt;October 23, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot; height=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; width=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/burnley-fan-celebrates-premier-league-win-over-everton-taking-horse-pub-video-161024214674</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 15:46:10 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617270494.jpg?itok=QybDO_tB" fileSize="134354" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Watch the fan celebrate Burnley&#039;s win below...</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/gettyimages-617270494.jpg?itok=uT6qAE41" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>WATCH: The INSANE goalmouth scramble from Crawley Town v Accrington Stanley</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/watch-insane-goalmouth-scramble-crawley-town-v-accrington-stanley-161024214671</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Goalmouth scrambles are one of the highlights of any football match, as the tension and suspense is unlike any other situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the video below shows off one of the greatest ever scrambles, from Satruday&#039;s League Two match between Crawley Town v Accrington Stanley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game ended 0-0, but the visitors came so, so close to scoring with a passage of play which saw goal line clearances, the post being hit, crazy tackles and nightmare goalkeeping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#039;s a thrilling moment of football action, and you can check it out below...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;media_embed&quot; height=&quot;315px&quot; width=&quot;560px&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;315px&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/O-6BE0kKQqY?start=88&quot; width=&quot;560px&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


</description>
 <author>talkSPORT</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/watch-insane-goalmouth-scramble-crawley-town-v-accrington-stanley-161024214671</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 15:35:25 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/drive1.jpg?itok=qNhfBGXn" fileSize="32371" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Watch the crazy goalmouth action below...</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/drive1.jpg?itok=VTq2v3L6" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Five things we learned about Tottenham from their 0-0 draw with Bournemouth</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/football/five-things-we-learned-about-tottenham-their-0-0-draw-bournemouth-161024214665</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;Tottenham remain the only unbeaten team in the Premier League this season as they were held to a 0-0 draw by Bournemouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cherries stopped Spurs playing with an impressive display at the Vitality Stadium, with the visitors looking frustrated for much of the match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mauricio Pochettino rued their inability to win the game, claiming a lack of freshness, on the back of a 0-0 Champions League draw with Bayer Leverkusen, cost them dear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what did we learn about Spurs from their performance against Bournemouth? Click the right arrow above to find out…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>Anton Stanley</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/football/five-things-we-learned-about-tottenham-their-0-0-draw-bournemouth-161024214665</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 15:34:08 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:group> <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/thfc-1.jpg?itok=zh-TQeJm" fileSize="46101" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">The duo were vital last season as Spurs battled at the top of the Premier League table. This year, both appear to have lost some of the spark which saw them as certain starters for Mauricio Pochettino. Lamela’s growth as a player since his move to White Hart Lane has been impressive but currently he’s operating below par both in open play and on set-pieces. The same can be said for Christian Eriksen who, like the Argentine, needs to step up a little more and become a match-winner, especially with Harry Kane and Toby Alderweireld absent.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/thfc-2.jpg?itok=YZW18IgS" fileSize="22528" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">In the absence of Harry Kane, Pochettino has used both Vincent Janssen and Heung-Min Son as strikers. The latter got the nod as the Argentine looked for a more dynamic approach, which worked against Manchester City. But as the game wore on, the introduction of Janssen changed very little about Tottenham’s play. The Argentine needs to work on how to use his substitutions to change the flow of a game. His move to put Moussa Sissoko into the game on the right wing also failed to add spark when, perhaps, it may have been better to push Mousa Dembele further forward and bring Harry Winks into a deep-lying role alongside Victor Wanyama.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/thfc-3.jpg?itok=dhMCDzLO" fileSize="47583" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">In certain matches, like against Man City, the South Korean works perfectly as a forward but it’s easy to see his best performances have been on the flanks this season, terrorising the likes of Jason Denayer, George Friend, and Geoff Cameron. His pace and directness when going forward puts teams on the back foot but, when leading the line against more defensive outfits, he struggles to find the space needed to make an impact.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/thfc-5.jpg?itok=5Ja112Ij" fileSize="42917" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">In recent weeks, Pochettino has been favouring a 4-1-4-1 formation, rather than last year’s 4-2-3-1, with a good degree of success. The problem against Bournemouth is three of the midfielders ahead of Victor Wanyama - Christian Eriksen, Dele Alli, and Mousa Dembele - all drifted towards the left side of the pitch, giving Erik Lamela a lack of support over on the right flank. This meant the Argentine moved centrally, making Spurs’ play look fairly predictable and led to the underuse of Kyle Walker. A bit more balance may have allowed the Lilywhites to open up their opponents, or at least stretch them and create more space.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/thfc-6.jpg?itok=u3BX9SAU" fileSize="28276" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">In the first half against Bournemouth, Tottenham looked extremely frustrated at their inability to get going at the Vitality Stadium. This resulted in bookings for Lamela, Jan Vertonghen, Dele Alli and Danny Rose. Last season Spurs committed plenty of fouls and earned a lot of cautions, but appeared to have cleaned up their act this time out. Pochettino needs to ensure this match is just an aberration, or risk losing key players to suspensions.</media:title>
</media:content>
</media:group>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/thfc-1.jpg?itok=tFrAuOI7" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/thfc-2.jpg?itok=UqHio82Z" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/thfc-3.jpg?itok=QJOC7bQ5" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/thfc-5.jpg?itok=YG309NGk" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/thfc-6.jpg?itok=ywnmNYbs" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
 <item> <title>Anthony Joshua v Klitschko off? 15 opponents British heavyweight world champion could fight next and who is most likely</title>
 <link>http://talksport.com/boxing/anthony-joshua-v-klitschko-15-opponents-british-heavyweight-world-champion-could-fight-next</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s no wonder some people say boxing is in decline…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fact it has taken this long for the WBA to come to a decision over whether or not to sanction Anthony Joshua v Wladimir Klitschko for their world heavyweight title is absolute madness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’d have thought it’d be pretty straight forward, but unfortunately this hasn’t turned out to be the case and it now looks most likely that, when the WBA announce their decision this week, Anthony Joshua will be left looking for a new opponent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IBF rules stipulate that Joshua’s opponent must either be another champion or someone from the top 15 of their own rankings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With lineal champ (the man who beat the man) Tyson Fury sidelined due to his many unfortunate issues and WBC king Deontay Wilder unable to make this December date through injury, Joshua is now left to go through the IBF rankings and pick someone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WARNING: It’s not a pretty list!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To see who Joshua could fight next from the IBF’s top 15 rankings click the right arrow on the picture above.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Here’s an honourable mention for Luis Ortiz who Eddie Hearn seems to be taking down the WBA route. A fight between him and Joshua won’t be happening at present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.P.S. Bermane Stiverne and Alexander Povetkin were recently removed from the IBF rankings after agreeing to fight for the WBC interim title and so are not on this list.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
 <author>Michael Benson</author>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">http://talksport.com/boxing/anthony-joshua-v-klitschko-15-opponents-british-heavyweight-world-champion-could-fight-next</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 15:13:08 +0100</pubDate>
 <source url="http://talksport.com/mrss2/all/all/mrss2sans">talkSPORT</source>
 <media:group> <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/teperhammer.jpg?itok=baNPSDea" fileSize="30727" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">We&#039;ve got a confusing one to start off with as Erkan Teper was IBF ranked #15 at the beginning of this month but has since lost to Christian Hammer and so will now surely fall out of the rankings. Perhaps Hammer will take Teper&#039;s place, but the problem with the Romanian as a potential Joshua opponent is that he&#039;s lost four times in his career and was comprehensively beaten by Tyson Fury in his one previous performance in the UK.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/jennings.jpg?itok=X0sJop7H" fileSize="35920" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Just a quick bonus slide to chuck in here, it is also possible that Bryant Jennings may take Teper’s place in the IBF rankings. Jennings wouldn&#039;t actually be a bad fight for Joshua, relative to the some other options available, as he&#039;s only lost twice: to Wladimir Klitschko and Luis Ortiz.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/hughiefury.jpg?itok=SZyC01MR" fileSize="34975" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Cousin of now former unified world champion Tyson, Hughie Fury is an interesting young prospect. The 22-year-old heavyweight has thus-far beaten everyone put in front of him, but doesn&#039;t look likely to face Joshua next as promoter Eddie Hearn says Fury&#039;s team want too much money for the fight.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/izuagbe.jpg?itok=ZuPn0rbv" fileSize="51335" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Poland’s Izuagbe Ugonoh is something of an unknown quantity in the heavyweight division at the moment. The unbeaten 29-year-old has been fighting out of Poland and New Zealand so far in his career and has yet to be properly tested. It is extremely unlikely he will face Joshua next.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/price.jpg?itok=KCzlD_if" fileSize="54179" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Despite apparently being one of the current front-runners to face Joshua on December 10, David Price would not be a popular choice with many fans. The Liverpudlian has lost three times in his career and, although the losses were disputed due to failed drugs tests from his opponents in the aftermath, these defeats asked serious questions that Price&#039;s chin unfortunately couldn’t answer.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/martin.jpg?itok=f1PQK30_" fileSize="46267" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Anyone fancy the rematch!?!?!? We thought not. </media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/chisora.jpg?itok=pb1IWaTT" fileSize="40436" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Technically, as he&#039;s ranked at #10 in the IBF rankings, Dereck Chisora could be eligible to face Anthony Joshua on December 10. However he has lost multiple times now and looks set to take on Dillian Whyte on that date instead, which should be an interesting fight in itself. </media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/miller.jpg?itok=B631Hvgp" fileSize="34507" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Unbeaten American Jarrell “Big Baby” Miller is one BIG baby and often weighs in at around 300lbs (21st 6lbs). The 28-year-old has spoken out in the past about how Joshua ‘has no chin’, but he has not been heavily linked with the fight on December 10.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/molina.jpg?itok=DH_AKbuF" fileSize="38748" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Since losing to Deontay Wilder in 2015, Eric Molina has come back with a strong KO win against Tomasz Adamek which indicates that he may not be a terrible potential fight for Joshua at the moment. In an ideal world Molina would face David Price next with the winner perhaps getting this shot at Joshua, however we don&#039;t live in an ideal world.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/glazkov.jpg?itok=tMR5Y1hX" fileSize="41347" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">This Ukrainian has only lost once, back in January, when he fought for the IBF title stripped from Fury. Glazkov picked up an injury in the third round which handed the title to his opponent Charles Martin. However it must be said that Glazkov looked poor in those early rounds and was arguably getting outboxed by Charles Martin. For that reason, a Joshua-Glazkov match up is really not that appealing.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/takam.jpg?itok=Bs9xYbrb" fileSize="39199" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Having recently agreed to fight fellow Frenchman Johann Duhaupas for the WBC silver title, Carlos Takam is very unlikely to face Joshua next.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/ruiz.jpg?itok=hT-jInSS" fileSize="37339" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Mexico’s Andy Ruiz Jr may have the best numerical record (29-0) of anyone in the IBF’s top 15, but he is not going to be the favourite when he fights Joseph Parker next for the WBO world title.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/duhaupas.jpg?itok=2sl-bHs1" fileSize="46744" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">As mentioned earlier, Johann Duhaupas looks set to face Carlos Takam for the WBC silver title next and so is out of contention to face Joshua. This is a shame as Duhaupas is a clearly durable opponent who took Deontay Wilder 11 rounds and could’ve possibly tested Joshua.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/haye_0.jpg?itok=c3C3Ucl7" fileSize="44936" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">What to say about David Haye? The former WBA champion would be a huge fight for Joshua, but promoter Eddie Hearn has ruled out making it for now as he seems to think Haye is about to sign a deal with rival TV network Boxnation. He is still trying to make Haye v Bellew though..?</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/pulev_2.jpg?itok=mr3madWP" fileSize="54011" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">This is the man Eddie Hearn should go all out for. If any of the potential opponents mentioned here could actually provide Joshua with a real test at the moment then it&#039;s Kubrat Pulev. Pulev is the current European Champion having recently beat Dereck Chisora to win the title, and has only lost once, to Wladimir Klitschko. The problem is, according to Hearn, Pulev is currently pricing himself out of the fight. Hopefully the situation can be resolved.</media:title>
</media:content>
 <media:content url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/large/public/field/image/201610/parker_0.jpg?itok=EohSCKMQ" fileSize="26431" type="image/jpeg" medium="image" width="700" height="420"> <media:title type="plain">Exciting young New Zealander Joseph Parker is currently Anthony Joshua&#039;s mandatory challenger and looked set to face the Londoner early next year. That was until Tyson Fury vacated his belts. Now it seems Parker will chase the WBO title instead and face Andy Ruiz Jr instead of Joshua. </media:title>
</media:content>
</media:group>
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/teperhammer.jpg?itok=20KFqq4g" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/jennings.jpg?itok=YCxMKIFT" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/hughiefury.jpg?itok=E5zbwcOv" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/izuagbe.jpg?itok=Wy2zeiyG" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/price.jpg?itok=Rxd7gMZw" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/martin.jpg?itok=lfqxMor8" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/chisora.jpg?itok=GQ_4C4IT" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/miller.jpg?itok=YJY6U0U8" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/molina.jpg?itok=uMESD4Ah" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/glazkov.jpg?itok=PZjbJVkn" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/takam.jpg?itok=p0G6BEs6" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/ruiz.jpg?itok=0WWzIfjn" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/duhaupas.jpg?itok=Ko7ct-s6" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/haye_0.jpg?itok=ehSGxLlP" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/pulev_2.jpg?itok=FqroAQyU" width="100" height="66" />
 <media:thumbnail url="http://talksport.com/sites/default/files/styles/thumbnail/public/field/image/201610/parker_0.jpg?itok=MH2NIsYK" width="100" height="66" />
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
